For starters, you have to know how to pair your shoes with the right outfit.
If you're wearing a dress, such as a short dress, you can wear large, clunky shoes that may or may not match your outfit.
One of my favorite things to do is to wear large wedge shoes with a short, cute cocktail dress.
Also what you can do is this: today I'm wearing a pair of jeans that I paired up with some heels.
If you take a look at these shoes... which I actually got from a fashion sale, directly from the designer.
They're kind of fun.
They may not go with every outfit but I have a pretty plain top and jeans on.
And since they are heels, they can actually make your legs look longer and that can help out any body and any figure when you wear jeans.
Boots are also a versatile and popular thing this winter.
You can wear them over jeans, under jeans, or here you can pair them with leggings and they have a slenderizing affect.
Join us in the next segment and we're going to be talking about how to accessorize with a belt.